A proxy confession service, huh?
Y-Yeah. We were thinking of using
the lunchtime broadcast for that.
You know the school rules.
Relationships aren't allowed on paper.
So we didn't want to be found out.
That rule's not really
enforced, though, right?
So, can we go ahead with it?
Nope. Sounds like a pain.
Saw that coming!
I don't want to get in trouble.
You and your
never-rock-the-boat attitude!
My life goal is to go to the grave
without ever making waves.
Why did she even become a teacher?
Ando-sensei.
It's an honor to finally meet you.
Please allow yours truly to enlighten you
on the benefits of this service.
You're annoying. And fired.
What?!
This is why I didn't
want boys in this club.
All you think about is being popular,
so you always act like you're hot shit.
Th-This is tyranny!
Please, Lemon-chan.
I really want to do this.
It's not every day you stick
to your guns, Uzuki.
But it's still a no.
Because this sounds like a pain.
Yeah, why did she become a teacher?
There's something in it
for you too, Lemon-chan.
Our club bombed last year's sports day,
but we're nailing it this year, right?
I suppose.
Are you aware?
Your stock is rising fast right now.
If this event goes well too,
your stock as a teacher
will go through the roof.
A peaceful life is nice and all,
but the view from the top
of the world is pretty great, too.
What are you standing around for?
We've got work to do.
What a self-serving teacher.
So...
What's first on the list?
Handing out flyers on the sly.
That's not happening.
Take a look.
Listen up! Boys and girls sit separately!
No relationships until you're twenty!
Ugh.
Get away!
It's Samejima, the P.E. teacher.
He's watching the students during lunch.
Just try handing those flyers out
where he can see.
PROXY CONFESSIONS
It'll be a scandal before you know it.
True...
What now? People can't
show up if they don't know.
We could use the group chats.
We won't reach the first-
and third-years with that.
Hey, why do you think I'm here?
To slack?
I'll distract Samejima.
I can buy you ten minutes at most.
Hand them out in that time.
Lemon-chan!
Thank you!
Now hurry!
Operation Lemon is underway!
Quit taking credit.
Quit taking charge.
You there! Stop talking
to the girls for no reason!
Break the rules, and you'll have to
write an apology letter on the spot!
So annoying.
His pecs are gross.
Sensei sees all! Remember that!
Samejima-sensei.
You're working so hard.
Why don't we teachers
take a quick break, too?
Oh, but...
I'm on supervision duty.
A quick break... A quickie, if you will?
Let's take a break
until the turn of the century!
We can rest in the shade.
Of course!
She sucks at winking.
Now's our chance! Hand those flyers out!
We're the broadcasting club.
We're holding a lunchtime event.
Feel free to take part.
Don't tell the teachers.
What's happening?
That sounds fun!
Whoa! I got a flyer from Himekawa-san!
Don't be so loud about it!
We do need to grab attention
to let everyone know.
What do we do? We can't be
too loud, or Sensei will notice.
How to catch the eye...
Oh, gather round, broadcasting club.
You're dismissed, errand boy.
So I've got a great idea.
What?
Well...
N-No way.
Hey, it's a fun idea.
I'm down.
I don't mind.
Well, I'm against it.
Just do it, Rikka.
Do this for Shinobu
and make her event a hit.
Hey, look!
Whoa! What's going on?
We're the broadcasting club.
We're hosting an event at lunch,
and everyone can participate.
P-Please join us.
Have a flyer.
Squee! Rikka-chan's cute!
Uzuki-san's adorbs!
Look this way, Nene-chan!
What's happening? Let's go check it out!
Good thing I left my costumes at school.
I-It's kind of embarrassing, though.
A moustache?
You owe me some cake later, Shinobu.
Ah, they're brute-forcing it.
I can see why they
didn't need an errand boy.
Y-Yamabuki!
I can't do this! This operation is over!
You've got explosive speed!
Hey! Why'd you bring him here?!
Hmm?
What's with that crowd?
Hey! What are you doing?
Yikes.
Retreat!
Hey, hold it!
State your names!
That was close!
I lost my pom-poms.
That was spine-tingling.
I'm never doing that again.
But we're all set.
Now we just pray that people
who want to confess show up.
Let's go over the process one more time.
CONFESSORS
IKO-NENE-RIKKA-SHINOBU
First, the confessors will wait
in the next classroom.
We'll be standing by there
to assist them, too.
The room's dark, so nobody
can see who's in there.
Privacy is guaranteed.
BROADCASTING ROOM (TEMP)
When it's their turn,
they'll go use the string phone
by the broadcasting room's door.
Shinobu, you sure about listening to
and broadcasting the confessions yourself?
Yeah, I want to do this.
Cool.
Okay, girls.
Let's do this.
Yeah.
Let's show them what the
broadcasting club can do this year!
Right!
Wow, this is actually happening.
Oh, no!
I'm getting nervous!
But if I can't do this, I have no hope.
Wait, we have a visitor already?
The event only starts at lunch...
Y-Yes.
Coming.
Okay, your confession, please.
Flub your lines,
and you'll have to do a dare.
Stay calm and keep it together, okay?
Hey! Don't prank me!
Sheesh... Who was that?
Who do you think it was?
Were you able to hear it?
Yeah, but...
It was over the string phone, so...
I CAN'T TELL WHOSE VOICE IT WAS
The morning events have concluded
with Team White in the lead.
TEAM RED - TEAM WHITE
We'll now break for lunch.
The proxy confessions will now
commence as announced.
What? Confessions?
Samejima-sensei.
Why don't we have lunch together?
Yes! I am the eater of worlds!
If you want to make a confession,
please head to the empty classroom
on the third floor of the main building.
Please.
Here comes the first confession.
"There's someone I've liked for so long.
It's Shindo-kun from Class 2-A.
I've been in love with you
ever since the day we first spoke.
If you know who I am—
if you're willing to accept my feelings—
would you please stand up?
That's all for my confession."
What is this broadcast?
Hey, this is great.
Samejima-sensei might lose it, though.
Wh-Why don't we go get
protein shakes sometime?
Wow, that's amazing.
Here comes the next confession.
Maybe I should go for it, too.
Wanna sneak out?
Shindo, you lucky dog!
There was a real chance
nobody would show up,
but I guess I had
nothing to worry about.
Wow, they're getting all hyped about it.
Everybody loves relationship talk, huh?
Curtains closed, Nene.
If we let sunlight in,
it'll reveal the confessors' faces.
Oops, my bad.
Anyway, this is a huge hit, right?
Are we awesome or what?
Well, it's Shinobu's event.
We're gonna be partying tonight!
Shinobu's plan really worked out, huh?
People want to express their feelings
with their voice, not letters or texts.
But phone calls can get awkward, so
we give them the perfect alternative...
with our proxy service.
"Takahashi-san
from Class 1-D, I love you!"
Dunno who you are, but I'm sorry!
I already have a boyfriend!
Damn, someone got rejected!
I said curtains closed!
By the way, you two...
Do you have anything you want to confess?
Oh, uh, I mean...
It can be something other than
expressing your feelings, you know.
Huh? Oh, I totally knew what you meant!
I do have something
I can't say to their face.
Me, too.
It's like...
There's this one person
who did a lot to help me.
But I butted heads with them
out of embarrassment.
I don't really care
what they think of me,
but I would like to say I'm sorry.
Huh...
As for me, what I'd like to confess is...
I was being really cold to someone.
I wanna tell him that he wasn't to blame,
and that it was all my fault.
I'm not exactly making myself clear, huh?
Oh, yeah?
And you, Iko?
Well, I was voice chatting with someone,
but I suddenly stopped talking
and made them freak out.
I just wanna, um, tell them
not to worry about it.
Hello?
I'd like to confess.
A visitor!
Come on in.
Don't worry. Nobody can see your face.
Huh? What's wrong?
It was just getting good!
What? Why?
It's not working.
Nope.
I'll break things even more
if I try to fix it.
Why am I always like this?
I always come up short when it counts.
At this rate...
I'll just prove her right.
Oh no... I'm going to cry...
Everything okay, Shinobu?!
Girls...
Hoo boy... I know the feeling.
The equipment stopped working!
Just when things were getting good!
Yeah, I have no idea.
We did upgrade some of our gear.
Maybe it's conflicting
with the older stuff.
Where's the errand boy?!
It's too bad, but we'll have
to put the event on hold.
On hold? But the lunch break will end!
Only one choice.
I'll broadcast the confessions
with my own voice.
Don't be silly!
You'll have to be super loud!
You'll wreck your throat.
Calm down, Shinobu.
But it'll be all over
if we don't do something.
Indeed.
It'll be all over...
unless yours truly comes
through to save the day.
Hey, where'd you get that?
Oh, I stole it from Samejima-sensei.
Look, a UFO!
What, where?
The teamwork between Lemon-sensei
and I made this happen.
We don't know how long
it'll take to fix the setup.
So we might as well pretend
this was all part of the plan.
Broadcast your voice directly from here.
Hurry, now.
Our clients are waiting!
Strike while the iron's hot...
Thanks, Yamabuki-kun!
You always come through!
You're the best!
Least I could do.
I'm your partner in crime.
Go on.
Let's restart. We're keeping
a bunch of clients waiting.
S-Sorry.
You're right.
The PA broadcast is over.
Hey, it's Shinobu-chan.
I'll now be using this megaphone
to deliver the confessions.
Please gather in the courtyard.
The courtyard!
Let's go.
"Mihara-kun from Class 3-A.
I'm in love with you."
Dammit, why Mihara?!
It's kinda like getting a confession
from Uzuki-san herself.
"We first met up
in the light music club..."
I'm glad it worked out.
Let's get back to the waiting room, too.
Huh? Where'd Yamabuki-kun go?
"If you can tell who I am,
I'll be waiting there
after sports day is over.
That's all."
I did it somehow.
Another one already?
I'll be right there!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
What would you like
to confess, and to whom?
The one I want to confess to is...
YAMABUKI ARISU-KUN.
"Here's my confession.
You know that hole in the wall
behind the gym?
I was the one who put it there.
Sorry about that!"
Okay, which idiot confessed to a crime?
Don't make Shinobu-chan say that crap.
Why aren't you in your gear, Yamabuki?
I'm done with all the events
I'm participating in.
It's only logical that
I switch back to my uniform.
Is it?
The broadcasting club will be
even busier in the PM.
So I'm eschewing being
sorry in favor of being safe.
Someone shut him up.
Lunch break will be over soon.
The next confession will be the last one.
What?!
You were all so brave.
I'm sorry we can't deliver
all your confessions.
Wait, she hasn't flubbed
her lines even once today.
Here's my confession.
I betrayed someone who gave me
so much support three years ago,
and I vanished from his life.
I didn't give a reason
or even say goodbye...
because I felt that I no longer
had any right to talk to him.
What's all this about?
Is it a couple that broke up?
I ran away from you.
I didn't think I could keep our promise.
Is this... No, it can't be.
It's a promise, then.
I'll work like my life's on the line, too,
so let's go see the pro world together!
That's why I was so shocked
when I heard your voice again.
At the same time, I was scared.
I figured you might be mad at me
for breaking our promise.
But instead...
I declare here and now
that I will guide all the members
of the broadcasting club
and turn them into true professionals!
You told me the same thing
you said back then.
So I'll return the favor and tell you
the same thing I said back then, too.
Arisu...
I love you.
That's all for the proxy
confession service.
Best of luck with the afternoon events!
Bye-bye!
Huh? What was that?
Was that a confession of love?
Arisu?
As in Yamabuki?!
What's going on, Yamabuki?
NOW STREAMING
MIDNIGHT HEART TUNE
To Apollo, "I love you"
was just how she signed off.
What she said now
should be no different...
But she'd never directed those words
to "Arisu" until now!
I must get to the bottom of this!
Hey, where are you going?
I went and said it.
Uzuki!
Sorry, can I ask you something?
Who was the last person
to make a confession...?
Th-That was all proxy, okay?!
I have no idea who made that confession!
I-I-It wasn't me, okay?!
Okay, just calm down!
She was this nervous?
Trying to identify Apollo here would go
against the intent of the proxy service.
Forgive me, Uzuki. I lost my cool.
I don't care who made that confession.
You did great with the proxy confessions.
It was a fantastic event.
I came here to tell you that.
Thank you!
Hey, you don't have to cry about it.
Because I bulldozed ahead with my idea!
I was so scared it'd fail!
I would've wasted the club's time!
O-Okay, let's take this
somewhere more private!
This could cause all kinds
of misunderstandings!
If Samejima-sensei sees us like this...
Who cares if he gets the wrong idea?
We can just get scolded together.
After all...
we're partners in crime, right?
I guess.
Hurry up and put all that stuff away.
Sports day isn't over
until the cleanup's done.
Then you help out too, Lemon-chan.
Why? Sports day is over,
so my job here is done.
Is it over or not?
You're giving mixed messages!
Samejima-sensei really raked me
over the coals for taking his megaphone!
I couldn't help with the cleanup.
I'll be getting an earful from the club!
APOLLO HAS STARTED STREAMING
"MIDNIGHT HEART TUNE"
APOLLO: I'M WAITING IN
THE BROADCASTING ROOM
Long time no talk.
Why the string phone?
I can't do this face-to-face.
It's been three years since we spoke.
What was the deal with
the proxy confession earlier?
I felt like I had to express my feelings.
I ran away from my radio show,
and I guess I'm just sick of hiding it.
While you're at it,
why not show yourself?
Yeah, I wish.
What if I said
I was actually fine with that?
That's why I asked you
to come here, anyway.
FLYBY ANOMALY
Translation:
Timing:
Editing:
Sriram Gurunathan
Mariana Martinez
William Haggard
Quality Check:
Translation Check:
S Bilyeu
Michelle Tymon